rohmhaas.com 2019-09-23

# Privacy Statement | Dow Legal Site

### Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement describes how The Dow Chemical Company and its affiliates (“Dow”) may collect information from or about you when you visit this website ([www.dow.com](https://www.dow.com/)) and other Dow websites that display or link to this Privacy Statement.

Dow values your privacy, and is providing this Privacy Statement to explain what information we collect and how that information may be used by Dow when you interact with Dow online.

In some countries, your use of Dow’s website could be considered consent by you to Dow’s use of this information. If you do not want us to collect or use your information as set out in this Privacy Statement, please do not use our websites or provide us with your information.

Please take a few minutes to review this Privacy Statement. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please [contact us](mailto:FGLPRIV@dow.com?subject=Dow%20Privacy%20Statement%20Question).

This Privacy Statement includes the following:  
Who Is Collecting Your Information  
What Information We Collect  
Additional Information for EU-based Users  
How Dow May Use and Share Your Information  
Location of Information  
Use of Special Features or Areas of Our Website  
Children’s Privacy  
Security  
External Links  
Changes to This Privacy Statement  
Your Choices  
Access, Update or Correct Your Personal Information  
Contact Dow

### Who Is Collecting Your Information

Information collected through [www.dow.com](https://www.dow.com/) is maintained by The Dow Chemical Company, Global Dow Center, 2211 H.H. Dow Way, Midland, Michigan 48674, and/or Dow’s affiliates. Dow can be reached through the contact information provided at the end of this Privacy Statement.

### What Information We Collect

When you interact with Dow online or in response to Dow’s marketing communications, Dow collects “Personal Data” about you, by which we mean information that may identify you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to Dow. Information that we collect includes the following:

_Information You Provide._

  * We collect the personal information you knowingly provide by completing an online form, registering for information or services, applying for a job, or otherwise sending to us. For example, if you sign up to receive e-mail communications from one of our businesses, we collect your e-mail address and any related information you provide. If you communicate with us using the “Contact Us” feature, we collect the information you provide when you complete the “Contact Us” form.
  * This includes information such as your name, email or physical address, or other contact details, or other records or copies of your correspondence with us (including emails).
  * If you sign up to receive e-mail communications from Dow, we will collect your e-mail address and any related information you provide.
  * If you communicate with Dow using the “Contact Us” feature, we collect the information you provide when you complete the “Contact Us” form.

_Supplemental Information._

  * In some cases, Dow may also collect information about you from other sources, and combine the information that you provide us online with other information that we have due to your relationship with Dow.
  * For example, if you are a Dow customer or supplier, we may use the information you have provided us both online and through our broader business relationships to improve your online experience.

_Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser._

  * As with many websites, we collect information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser.
  * This information typically includes your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the identity of your internet service provider, the name and version of your operating system and browser, the date and time of your visit, the page that linked you to Dow, and the pages you visit.

_Cookies and Other Technologies._

  * Dow may use “cookie” technology on this website; a cookie is a text file containing information which is sent by a website and stored in your computer’s hard drive or temporary memory.
  * You may change your cookie settings on your internet browser or delete our cookies at any time.
  * We use cookies to save your preferences for our websites or to collect statistics related to the number of visitors to our websites and requests for files, the types of browsers used, and other aggregate data.
  * Dow also uses transparent pixels (e.g. GIF, PNG, etc.) files to help manage online advertising by collecting information related to which advertisements drive traffic to our websites.
  * The specific types of cookies that are used on our website include the following:

   **First- And Third-Party Cookies**  
_Technical Cookies_   
Technical cookies are those necessary to display the information on the website properly, or otherwise used to carry out the transmission of a web communication. They are not used for any further purposes and are normally installed directly by the owner or the operator of the website.

Technical cookies can be divided into:

    * Browsing And Session Cookies: These cookies guarantee regular navigation and use of the site (e.g. allowing authentication to access restricted areas);
    * Analytics Cookies: These cookies are used to collect aggregate information on the number of visitors and on how they use the site.
    * Functional Cookies: These cookies allow the user to browse as a function of certain pre-determined criteria (e.g., the language, products selected for review, etc.) in order to improve the service offered.
  
**Profiling Cookies**  
Profiling cookies are aimed at creating user profiles and are used to send online advertising messages in line with the preferences shown by the user during navigation.

These cookies, either of the Company or of third parties, are accurately selected and checked and are used to guarantee that the marketing messages received through the site or other websites used by the Company to transmit its advertising messages are in line with the visitor’s preferences. This enables the potential to offer pertinent messages, based on previous visits to the site, on the pages visited more frequently and on other data concerning the visitor. Dow websites will only use profiling cookies with your prior consent.

**Cookies Used On Dow Websites**  
A comprehensive list of cookies that can be found on Dow websites is found below. For Third Party cookies, Dow or its supporting agencies do not define, aide in or determine what the vendor deems as non-personally identifiable information nor define consent or manage any consent mechanisms. Ultimately, these cookies are supplied by third parties who control the right to update the purpose or use of each.

FIRST PARTY COOKIES  
---  
**Category** | **Type** | **Duration** | **Purpose**  
Technical | Browsing/Session | Session | These are used with the only purpose to ensure that the site functions properly and to improve the service offered, as well as allowing easier browsing based on a set of criteria selected by the visitor (e.g.. language, country, form information and/or products selected for purchase). They are removed when the browser is closed.  
Technical | Functional | Permanent | They are used when user clicked Accept button on the Cookie Notification. This is stored to hide the cookie notification overlay on the next visit of the site.  
  
THIRD-PARTY COOKIES  
---  
**Category** | **Type/Provider** | **Duration** | **Purpose** | **Privacy policy & opt-out**  
Analytics Cookies | Adobe Analytics  
| Session and  
Permanent (2 years)  
| The purpose of these cookies is to differentiate requests from different browsers and to store helpful information that an application can use later. They may also be used to associate browsing information with non-identifiable user IDs. In particular, these cookies are used to anonymously define new visitors, help analyze clickstream data, and track historical activity on the website, such as response to particular campaigns. According to Adobe, these cookies are removed when the browser is closed.  
| 

For more information, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html>

To opt-out, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>  
  
Adobe Audience Manager  
| 5 Months | This cookie assigns a unique ID to a site visitor, which helps Audience Manger perform basic functions such as visitor identification, ID synchronization, segmentation, modeling, reporting, etc.  
| 

For more information, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html>

[](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html)To opt-out, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>  
  
everesttech.net / Adobe Marketing Cloud  
| 2 Hours - 2 Years  
| This ad exchange-specific cookie synchronizes the Media Optimizer user ID with the partner's ad exchange platform and records the date.  
| 

For more information, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html>

[](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html)To opt-out, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>  
  
Omniture / Adobe Marketing Cloud  
| 2 Years | These cookies are used to track site visitors by giving each visitor a unique visitor ID. Ideally, this is a persistent cookie with an extended expiration period.  
| 

For more information, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html>

[](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html)To opt-out, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>  
  
Google Analytics | Permanent (10 Minutes and 2 Years)  
| They are used to anonymously monitor visitor behavior on the site for statistical survey purposes, as well as to allow Dow to optimize the site performance and offer a better browsing experience.  
| 

For more information, click on <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>

[](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en)To opt-out, click on [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](http://https//tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)  
  
AddThis | 1 Year | These cookies are used for analytics reports using what the vendor describes as aggregate data for sharable social content on the page. It keeps track of the count of shared pages through “AddThis”.  
| 

For more information, click on <http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy>

To opt-out, click on <http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out>  
  
Facebook/Instagram | 1 Week - 2 Years  
| They are used to measure the performance of ad campaigns for businesses that use Facebook/Instagram products. These cookies help to serve and measure ads across different browsers and devices used by the same person. They also help you opt out of seeing ads from Facebook/Instagram based on your activity on third-party websites.  
| 

For more information, click on <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950?helpref=faq_content>

[](https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950?helpref=faq_content)For more information click on <https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/>  
  
Coveo | 2 Years | These cookies are used for tracking all the interactions with the Coveo search tool. A random unique value is generated with the user visits the site, and it is used to keep related metrics like the number of distinct users who submitted a query or click on an item.  
| For more information, click on <https://www.coveo.com/privacy>  
  
Twitter  
| 1 Week - 2 Years  
| These cookies collect data through a range of plug-ins and integration that is primarily used for tracking and targeting ads.  
| For more information and to opt-out, click on <https://business.twitter.com/en/help/ads-policies/other-policy-requirements/interest-based-opt-out-policy.html>  
  
Profiling Cookies | Google DoubleClick | 540 Days | These cookies are used to select online advertising messages based on what is pertinent to the visitor, in line with the information collected during browsing and to prevent the visitor from viewing previously displayed ads. Per the vendor, consent is requested for the use of these cookies.  
| 

For more information and to opt-out, click on <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/>

For further information, click on <https://support.google.com/dfp_premium/answer/2839090?hl=en>  
  
Facebook/Instagram | 90 Days | These cookies require consent and are used to select advertising messages in Facebook/Instagram consistent with a user’s preferences and interests based on information collected during the browsing of a site. According to the vendor, these adverts are served using what they define as non-personally identifiable information.  
| 

For more information, click on <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950?helpref=faq_content>

To opt-out, click on <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>  
  
AddThis | 1 Year | These cookies are used to keep track of masked activities and enables marketers to provide more targeted online advertising. They are usually presented in sites to allow users to share the content on various networking and sharing platforms.  
| 

For more information, click on <http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy>

To opt-out, click on <http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out>[  
](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out)  
  
Adobe Marketing Cloud | 2 Years | They are used to store unique visitor IDs used by Marketing Cloud Solutions. It tracks visitors across Dow’s different domains and enable data sharing among different Experience Cloud solutions and helps to personalize and improve the performance of the website.  
| 

For more information, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html>

[](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html)To opt-out, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>  
  
Adobe Target | 2 Years | These cookies are used for performance and statistics of marketing box content.  
| 

For more information, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html>

[](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html)To opt-out, click on <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>  
  
YouTube | 9 Months - 2 Years  
| These are used by Google for storing user preferences and other purposes as set forth by the vendor.  
| 

For more information, click on [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies](http://https//policies.google.com/technologies/cookies)

To opt-out, click on <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>[  
](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)  
  
Oracle Eloqua | 2 Years | They are used to store a unique Eloqua Customer ID (GUID) used to identify visitors on the site. Also, if a form is sent on the site, the information sent will be associated with the Eloqua cookie on the browser and will be used to personalize the communications and track the pages that are visited.  
| 

For more information click on <https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html>

To opt-out, click on <https://www.oracle.com/marketingcloud/opt-status.html>  
  
Amobee (formerly Adconian Media Group)  
| 6 Hours - 4 Years  
| These cookies are used to provide real-time bidding to sell targeted audience advertising space based on behavioral profiles.  
| 

For more information, click <https://www.amobee.com/trust/technology/#cookies>

To opt-out, click <http://www.amobee.com/trust/consumer-opt-out>  
  
Quantserve | 10 Months | They are used to track behavior on a website. Ultimately, this cookie is supplied by a third party who controls the right to update the purpose or use.  
| For more information and to opt-out, click <https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/>[  
](https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/)  
Quantcast | 1 Year | These cookies are used provide website rankings, and the data they collect is also used for audience segmentation and targeted advertising.  
| For more information and to opt-out, click <https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/>  
  
TripleLift | 1 - 2 Months | They provide programmatic native advertising services.  
| 

For more information, click <https://triplelift.com/privacy/>

To opt-out click <https://triplelift.com/consumer-opt-out/>[  
](https://triplelift.com/consumer-opt-out/)  
  
IPONWEB | 1 Year | These cookies are used to provide a real-time bidding platform for targeted online advertising.  
| For more information and to opt-out, click <http://www.bidswitch.com/policies/>[  
](http://www.bidswitch.com/policies/)  
QUMU  
| 30 Years | They are used for make the Qumu experience more convenient and personal. Their cookies help to better understand user behavior, preferences and usage of the video solution.  
| For more information, click on <https://qumu.com/en/privacy/>[  
](https://qumu.com/en/privacy/)  
LinkedIn | 1 Day -   
1 Year | This cookies collect anonymous data related to the user's visits to the website, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded, with the purpose of displaying targeted ads. | For more information and to opt-out, click <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy>  
  
**Deletion of Cookies, Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures**  
You are free to set your browser or operating system settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the site. Please refer to your web browser’s or operating system’s website or “Help” section for more information on how to delete and/or disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences.

Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. In addition, Dow’s system does not collect any information that can personally identify a specific individual based on their normal browsing activities. Rather, users must first openly provide individual information (e.g. through a Contact Us form submission) before there is any possibility of actual discrete tracking. To learn more about the use of cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to know your choices about not having this information used by certain service providers, please click <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/600424>.

On your mobile device, you may also adjust your privacy and advertising settings to control whether you want to receive more relevant advertising.

_Analytics._

  * Dow uses web analytics services including Adobe Experience Cloud products provided by Adobe Systems Incorporated (“Adobe”), and Google Analytics provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).
  * These analytics services use cookies (text files placed on your computer) to help Dow understand how you use our website. The information generated by the cookies about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Adobe and Google on servers in: the United States (Adobe); and the U.S. and other countries (Google).
  * Adobe and Google will use this information to provide data about your use of the website that allow creation of reports on website activity for website operators, and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.
  * Adobe and Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on their behalf.
  * Adobe and Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by either company.
  * You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. For German users, to opt out of Google Analytics tracking entirely, please visit the following link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de>.
  * Dow uses Qualtrics -- a third-party survey provider -- to solicit and gather qualitative user opinions of its websites. Filling out a survey is never a requirement to view a Dow website and is at the sole discretion of the user. Any data provided is transmitted to and stored by Qualtrics on servers in the United States.
  * Dow employs other peripheral technologies that complement dow.com, but are not a part of it. Examples include Oracle Eloqua – a marketing automation platform that deploys email campaigns and hosts related landing pages – and QUMU – an enterprise video platform that hosts and distributes live and on-demand video content. Both systems similarly follow the tracking standards enumerated for other technologies above.

_Ad Remarketing._

  * This website uses remarketing services such as Google AdWords, Facebook/Instagram, LinkedIn, DoubleClick, AddThis and others to advertise on third-party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site.
  * These remarketing services can be used in different ways, including:
    * Advertising to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry or to previous visitors who have viewed information on our products.
    * Displaying an advertisement on the Google search results page, a site in the Google Display Network, or on a social network.
    * Third-party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Dow website.
  * You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### Additional Information for EU-based Users

Data protection regulations in Europe require Dow to disclose additional information regarding Personal Data collected from European users, and to limit Dow’s use of such information in specific ways. This section provides additional information applicable to European Personal Data, which may not apply to users in other geographies.

_Legal Basis for Processing._  
European Personal Data may only be processed by Dow where and to the extent that such processing is:

  * Necessary for the performance of a contract with you, such as: 
    * To carry out Dow’s obligations with respect to any contractual agreements between us with respect to information, products, and services that you may request from Dow; 
    * To process a job application; or
    * To fulfill any other agreements between us.
  * Necessary for Dow to comply with a legal obligation, for example to meet our tax and accounting obligations.
  * Necessary to serve the legitimate business interests of Dow or a third party, where such use is consistent with the fundamental rights of individuals under European law, for example: 
    * To provide you with effective customer service or technical support, such as where you have requested information from Dow;
    * To contact you with information regarding health and safety, applicable regulations, or stewardship of our products;
    * To improve the content, functionality, performance, security and usability of our website;
    * To notify you about changes to our business, products, services, or our website;
    * To conduct business transactions, including purchases and sales of Dow products, or business reorganizations including the sale, transfer, change in control or merger of Dow assets or businesses.
  * Subject to a valid consent you have freely provided and not withdrawn, such as opt-in consents allowing Dow to place cookies on your computer or to use your contact information for promotional advertising.

_Data Subject Rights._  
European users of this website have the legal right to request Dow undertake specific actions with respect to their Personal Data, including:

  * The right to request access to your Personal Data, including the right to have Dow confirm if your Personal Data is being used by Dow;
  * The right to have your Personal Data corrected or erased;
  * The right to object to or restrict Dow’s use of your Personal Data, for example where such information is not accurate or no longer needed;
  * The right to have your Personal Data transferred from Dow to another party;
  * The right to not be subject to automated decision-making or profiling based on your Personal Data;
  * The right to withdraw any consent you have previously provided to Dow’s collection or use of your Personal Data; and
  * The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

_Cross-Border Transfers of Data._  
The information that Dow collects from you will be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us, or by other entities acting as data processors on our behalf. Dow has implemented international data transfer agreements on the basis of the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses in order to provide appropriate and suitable safeguards for the transfer of this information. You may request a copy of the Standard Contractual Clauses by contacting the privacy contact for your geographic region listed below.

_Data Retention._  
Dow will process and store your Personal Data for the duration of our relationship with you, which may be a long term, and as long as necessary to fulfill our contractual and legal obligations. Dow will delete your data:

  * When it is no longer necessary for the purposes for which that information was collected and processed;
  * Upon your request or objection, provided there are no overriding legal grounds requiring Dow to maintain that information;
  * When necessary to comply with Dow’s legal obligations; and
  * If our collection of information was based on your consent, upon the withdrawal of your consent.

Any requests or inquiries relating to Dow’s handling of EU information may be made by [contacting us](https://app.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/ffde346b-1286-4be1-9186-0dd389ded92c).

### How Dow May Use and Share Your Information

Subject to applicable local law, Dow may use the personal information we collect through our website for any legitimate and lawful business purpose, including but not limited to the following:

  * to provide products, information and services you request;
  * to provide you with effective customer service or technical support;
  * to contact you with information regarding health and safety, applicable regulations, or stewardship of our products;
  * to improve the content, functionality, performance and usability of our website;
  * to improve our marketing and promotional efforts;
  * to provide technical support and troubleshooting; and
  * for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
  * for any other purpose identified in an applicable privacy statement or other agreement you may have with Dow.

Dow may use or disclose aggregated or anonymized data about our users, if that information does not identify any individual, in Dow’s sole discretion.

Dow may share your information with Dow affiliates for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement. Dow may also share your information with third parties in specific cases such as:

  * _Our Service Providers._ We may share your personal information with companies or organizations, including subsidiaries, affiliates, and other entities that perform services on our behalf, such as marketing and website support service providers.
  * _Business Transactions and Transfers._ Dow may buy, sell, form, or otherwise reorganize one or more of its businesses or sell stock or assets, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization or liquidation. A transaction of this type may involve the disclosure of your information to prospective purchasers or partners who have signed a confidentiality agreement with Dow.
  * _Compliance with Laws and Protection of Our Rights and the Rights of Others._ We may disclose personal information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose personal information to cooperate with a government investigation; to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce or apply our online terms of use or other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.

Other than as described above, Dow does not provide or sell your personal information to third parties.

### Location of Information

Dow is a global organization with its corporate headquarters in the United States. Our servers, databases, and service providers are located in the United States and in other countries. Different countries have different privacy laws and requirements, and some, including the United States, may provide less legal protection for your personal information than others. If you object to the transfer of your information to the United States, please do not use Dow’s website or provide Dow with that information.

### Use of Special Features or Areas of Our Website

This Privacy Statement may be supplemented by additional privacy statements that may be specific to individual Dow websites or features, such as our investor and career sites. Dow’s websites may include special features such as surveys, licensed content, online stores, or password protected areas, such as a customer-only area or a careers area, and these areas or websites may be subject to additional terms of use or privacy statements which may further specify additional personal information Dow may collect in these areas, why we need that information, and choices you may have about the use of that information.

When you sign up to use a special feature or password-protected area, you may be asked to agree to additional terms governing your use of the special feature or password-protected area. In such cases, you may be asked to expressly consent to the additional terms, for example, by checking a box or clicking on a button marked “I agree.” (This type of agreement is known as a “click-through” agreement.) If any of the terms of a click-through agreement or another agreement between you and Dow are different than the terms of this Privacy Statement, the terms of that agreement will control over this Privacy Statement.

### Children's Privacy

Dow’s website is not intended for children under 16 years of age, and Dow does not knowingly collect information from children to sell or promote our products or services. No one under the age of 16 may provide information to Dow on or through our website, and if we learn that we have received information from a child under the age of 16, we will delete that information.

Dow may host educational programs in science for students and teachers in our communities, but we do not invite minors to contact us or provide us with personal information. Visitors must be 18 years of age or older to submit registration or survey information. Parents or legal guardians may register to obtain information or participate in a survey on behalf of their children.

If you believe a child under the age of eighteen has sent personal contact information to Dow, please [contact us](https://app.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/ffde346b-1286-4be1-9186-0dd389ded92c) immediately and we will use reasonable efforts to promptly remove that information from our systems.

### Security

We take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the confidentiality, integrity and security of your personal information. We urge users to be careful with personal information while using the Internet.

_SSL Protection._ Many Dow websites, including dow.com, are able to provide a secure connection between your computer and our server be established. We use an encryption technology called Secure Socket Layers (SSL). A secure connection is maintained until you leave the secure area of the site. Although we use SSL encryption to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information as it travels over the Internet, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet and we cannot guarantee the safety of transmitting personal information over the Internet.

_Password Protection._ You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your passwords. We have the right to assume that anyone accessing one of our websites using a password assigned to you has the right to do so. You will be solely responsible for the activities of anyone accessing our website using a password assigned to you, even if the individual is not, in fact authorized by you. If you have reason to believe that your password has been compromised or used without authorization, you must promptly change it using the functionality provided on the site or notify Dow that your account has been compromised.

### External Links

Some of our websites may contain links to other websites on the Internet that are not under the control of or maintained by Dow. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Dow of those websites, the content displayed, or the persons or entities associated with them. By visiting a linked website from a Dow website, you acknowledge that Dow is providing these links to you only as a convenience and you agree that Dow is not responsible for the content of such websites. External sites are governed by their own terms and policies and are not governed by Dow's Privacy Statement, Terms of Use, Accessibility Statement, or other terms and policies.

### Changes to This Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this site and updated effective date at the bottom of this page. As we add new features and functionality to our websites or Dow policies or applicable laws evolve, we may need to update or revise this Privacy Statement. We reserve the right to do so, at any time and without prior notice, by posting a revised version on our website. These changes will be effective as of the date we post a revised version on our website.

If we make changes to this Privacy Statement that materially change how we treat your personal data, we will make a reasonable effort to notify you promptly through reasonable means.

### Your Choices

We respect your right to make choices about how you would like to interact with Dow and the extent of the personal information you choose to share with Dow. In some cases, we will ask you to indicate your choices at the time we collect your personal information. If you have previously agreed to receive email or marketing communications from Dow, you may "opt-out" at any time by using the unsubscribe feature included in the e-mails we send.

### Access, Update or Correct Your Personal Information

If you have created an account or a personal profile on one of our websites, you may be able to access and update some or all of your personal information on your account settings or profile page. If you wish to access, update or correct other personal information, please [contact us](https://app.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/ffde346b-1286-4be1-9186-0dd389ded92c). We will contact you and may ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In most cases, we will update information as requested. In some cases, however, we may limit or deny your request if permitted or required by law or if we are unable to verify your identity.

### Contact Dow

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, you may contact us by phone at the numbers listed at <https://www.dow.com/en-us/contact>. You may also contact us via [email](mailto:FGLPRIV@dow.com?subject=Dow%20Privacy%20Statement%20Question). You may also send postal correspondence to:

**In the United States:**  
The Dow Chemical Company  
Data Privacy Director  
2211 H.H. Dow Way  
Midland, Michigan 48674  

**In Canada:**  
Dow Chemical Canada ULC.  
Privacy Officer  
2100- 450 1 ST SW Calgary AB T2P 5H1  
403-267-3527  

DowAgroSciencesCanada Inc.  
Privacy Officer  
2100- 450 1 ST SW Calgary AB T2P 5H1  
403-735-8861  

**In Europe:**  
Dow Benelux Integrated Center B.V.  
Dow Customer Information Group  
Herbert H. Dowweg 5  
4542 NM Hoek, The Netherlands

**In Asia-Pacific:**  
Dow Chemical MalaysiaSdnBhd  
Level 6, CP Tower,Jalan16/11  
PusatDagang, Section 16  
46350PetalingJaya  
SelangorDarulEhsan  
Malaysia

**In Latin America:**  
DowQuimicaS.A.   
RuaAlexandre Dumas 1671   
ChacaraSanto Antonio   
São Paulo   
Brazil 04717-903

If you have concerns that someone affiliated with Dow has used your information in a manner that is not appropriate, you may also contact the Dow EthicsLine. The Dow [EthicsLine](https://corporate.dow.com/en-us/about/beliefs-and-culture/ethics) can be accessed using a toll-free help line, with multi-lingual capabilities, available 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, worldwide. The Dow EthicsLine can also be accessed using an [online form](https://secure.ethicspoint.com/domain/media/en/gui/23573/index.html) that provides the option of submitting a written report. In addition, you always have the option of contacting the [Office of Ethics and Compliance](https://corporate.dow.com/en-us/about/beliefs-and-culture/ethics) at 989-636-2544 or via email [Ethics@Dow.com](mailto:Ethics@Dow.com).

Effective Date: May 11, 2018
